It's not just a documentary. It's a social experiment.
Am I Racist? is a comedy, documentary film directed by Justin Folk.
Matt Walsh goes deep undercover in the world of
diversity, equity, and inclusion.
Prepare to be shocked by how far race hustlers will go and how much further Matt Walsh will
go to expose the grift, uncovering absurdities that will leave you laughing.
Self, played by Matt Walsh.
Self, played by Robin DiAngelo.
Self, played by Regina Jackson.
Self, played by Saira Rao.
Self, played by Regan Byrd.
Self, played by Sarra Tekola.
Am I Racist?
is a 2024 American satirical documentary comedy film starring conservative political commentator
Matt Walsh that lampoons the diversity, equity, and inclusion (DEI) movement.
Directed by Justin Folk for The Daily Wire, it follows Walsh as he poses as a "bumbling DEI
trainee", using subterfuge to interview experts and attend anti-racism workshops.
The film has been described as a mockumentary in the style of Borat.
With a production budget of $3 million, the film was theatrically
released in the United States on September 13, 2024.
It grossed $12.3 million, becoming the
highest-grossing documentary film of 2024.
The film explores themes of politics, racism,
disguise, obnoxious, self-loathing.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.